# **CÉSAR MOLTÓ MORILLA**

#### VIDEO GAME PROGRAMMER

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a Spanish video game programmer with +2 years of experience in the gaming industry and strong knowledge of Unreal Engine and Unity3D, who loves creating interactive experiences that players find immersive and impressive.

My passions are technology, sports and travelling. And when I am not working or studying, I like playing competitive video games, watching movies, and doing outdoor sports and martial arts.

# SKILLS

C / C++ / C# / JAVA / GLSL / BLUEPRINTS (UE4 **VISUAL SCRIPTING)** 

UNREAL ENGINE 4 / UNITY 3D / OPENGL / VISUAL STUDIO / ANDROID STUDIO

GRAPHICS PROGRAMMING / GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMING / VR PROGRAMMING

GIT / MERCURIAL / PERFORCE / TRELLO / **SLACK** 

TEAM WORK / AGILE METHODS / PROJECT MANAGEMENT

### LANGUAGES

#### **SPANISH**

Native Proficiency | Mother tongue

#### **ENGLISH**

Professional working proficiency | C1

#### **GERMAN**

Elementary Proficiency | A2

#### **JAPANESE**

Elementary Proficiency | N5

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

#### **EMAIL**

cmoltomorilla@gmail.com

#### **WEBSITE**

https://cesarmolto.github.io

#### **PHONE NUMBER**

+34620893530

#### LINKEDIN

César Moltó Morilla

# **EDUCATION**

**REY JUAN CARLOS UNIVERSITY** 

MADRID, SPAIN

Master in Computer Graphics, Games and Virtual Reality 2021 - Present

#### UNIVERSITY OF ALICANTE

ALICANTE, SPAIN

Multimedia Engineering Degree

2016 - 2021

• GPA: 7.90 / 10

#### ATHLONE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

**IRELAND** 

Software Engineering Exchange Year (Erasmus K103)

2018 - 2019

• GPA: 8.93 / 10

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **HANDY GAMES**

#### WÜRZBURG, GERMANY

Game programmer

September 2020 - May 2021

- Ported the game Titan Quest: Legendary Edition to the Android and IOS platforms.
- Implementation of game controller support, game rules, rendering of controller-specific graphics, UI elements and animations.
- · Performed memory and rendering optimization, testing and troubleshooting for bugs and ensured correct documentation.

#### **4FREAKSFICTION**

ZARAGOZA, SPAIN

Game programmer

October 2018 - September 2020

- · Worked as a volunteer programmer on the development of several video game prototypes for pc and mobile platforms with Unity3D.
- · Coordinated code remotely with other programmers to prototype and implement new gameplay features; i.e., combat and interaction mechanics, player controls, enemy AI, etc...

# **PROJECTS**

#### **DODGEBALL MASTERS**

Gaphics and gameplay programmer, and Project Manager

Supervised and programmed a dodgeball multiplayer game with 8 playable characters and +20 unique skills using C++ and OpenGL.

More information: https://cesarmolto.github.io/dodgeball-masters.html

#### **BATTLE TANK**

Solo project

Developed a head-to-head tank fight game with Al-controlled enemies, pathfinding, and an advanced control system in UE4.

More information: https://cesarmolto.github.io/battle-tank.html

#### **ROOM MAKER VR**

Graphics programmer, Designer and Project Manager

Led a 4 people team into programming and designing a Virtual Reality scenario editor with Unity 3D and VR Oculus hardware.

More information: https://cesarmolto.github.io/room-maker.html